fashos.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

You have no items in your shopping cart.

We would want our guests to feel secure when shopping with us. We are committed to keeping your information secure.

  * **Personalization Survey:** FASHOS is committed to providing you a personalized shopping experience. Before you start shopping with FASHOS we want to know your likes and preferences through Know your style survey. This data is used to create your personalized store at our site and content that our stylists recommend for you mapped with your preferences.
  * **Data Profiling:** We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you sign up for your personalized store with FASHOS. The information provided by you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our Guests' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. Your personal information is utilized to fulfill the services you request. In case your information is utilized towards any marketing initiatives derived by FASHOS, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our user activity on our website in order to provide you best of the class services and offers. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.
  * **Cookies:** These are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to FASHOS e.g. your IP address, how you entered & navigated this website what pages were of interest to you etc. (please note that if you are uncomfortable with the use of cookies, they can be disabled on your computer by changing the preferences or options menu in the browser settings).
  * **My Store and Payment Information:** Guests account history/information including (without limitation) all billing information and communications, payment history etc are maintained in an encrypted format on secure servers. Please note FASHOS does not store your credit card or online bank account information.
  * **Safety Measures:** Our website abides by strict security instructions in order to protect your personal information against unauthorized access like theft, misuse and alteration. We offer use of secure servers in order to preserve guest s personal data.
  * **Linking Sites:** FASHOS is not responsible for privacy practices or content posted on linking websites. We highly recommend out guests to go through the respective privacy policies before providing any personal information.

**Note:** Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. Feel free to get in touch with our Guest Care team at [guestrelations@fashos.com](mailto:guestrelations@fashos.com) for any queries related to Privacy Statement.
